Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series X is arranged in 18 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series X. BYLAWS - GENERAL CHAIRMENS' ASSOCIATION
  - Sub-Series 207-1. Bylaws
    - Associations of General Chairmen-New York Central Railroad (N. Y. C. R.R.), 1932-1957 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 207-1. Bylaws
    - Associations of General Chairmen-New York Central Railroad, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 207-2. Bylaws
    - Association of General Chairmen-Illinois Central, 1935-1936 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 207-3. Bylaws
    - Association of General Chairmen-Pittsburgh (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 207-5. Bylaws
    - Association of General Chairmen-Pennsylvania Board of Adjustment, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 207-6. Bylaws
    - Association of General Chairmen-Grand Trunk, 1949-1953 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 207-7. Bylaws
    - N. C. & St. L. Association of General Chairmen, 1949-1956 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 207-9. Bylaws
    - General Chairmen's Association of the Standard Railroad Labor Organizations on the Atlantic Coast Line Railroad and Allied Lines, 1951 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 207-10. Bylaws
    - Association of General Chairmen-Erie Railroad, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 43)
      1952 June 12
  - Sub-Series 207-11. Bylaws
    - Association of General Chairmen-Reading Company, 1952-1953 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 207-12. Bylaws
    - Association of General Chairmen-Seaboard Air Line, 1952-1955 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 207-13. Bylaws
    - Association of General Chairmen-St. Louis Southwestern Railroad, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 207-14. Bylaws
    - Association of General Chairmen-Kansas City Terminal, 1952-1957 (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 207-15. Bylaws
    - Association of General Chairmen-Rutland Railway, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 48)
      Jan. 2, 1953.
  - Sub-Series 207-18. Bylaws
    - Association of General Chairmen-Fort Dodge, Des Moines & Southern Railway, 1953-1956 (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 207-19. Bylaws
    - Association of General Chairmen-Denver & Rio Grande Western, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 207-21. Bylaws
    - Association of General Chairmen-Gulf, Mobile & Ohio, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 51)
      Sept. 24, 1955.
  - Sub-Series 207-22. Bylaws
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis (M. & St. L.) General Chairmen's Association, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 52)